bestfoodrecipe.info 2016-01-21

# Best Food Recipe

bestfoodrecipe.info, consider your privacy to be of the upmost importance. The Privacy Policy outlined below explains the way in which we deal with the information collected when you visit bestfoodrecipe.info (“the Site”).

## Personal Information:

bestfoodrecipe.info promises never to sell your personal information to a third party without your express permission. However, it may be necessary for us to reveal your personal information in the following instances: a) should we be required to do so by law or court order; b) to protect the legal rights or property of bestfoodrecipe.info; c) in connection with a transfer or disposition of bestfoodrecipe.info and/or the Site; and/or d) to a third party in connection with their provision of technical services.

## Anonymous Information: 

From time to time, bestfoodrecipe.info may ask you for non-personally identifiable information, such as household income, age or lifestyle preferences such as your latest likes and dislikes. You are under no obligation to respond to these requests and we promise to still allow you to use the Site. Should you choose to help us we will not only be eternally grateful but will use this data to improve your user experience. In order to do this we may need to share this information with other third parties, such as potential advertisers. However, we promise this will always be in anonymous form and will therefore not contain any personally identifiable information.

## Usage Information: 

In addition to the above, bestfoodrecipe.info will collect non-personally identifiable information about the way in which you, our followers, use the Site. This can be anything from the amount of time you spend on the Site to the links you click on whilst on the Site. This information is not personally identifiable and will not only help us provide valuable information to our advertisers (so we can ensure the longevity of the Site) but will also enable us to make sure the Site can function effectively from a technical perspective.

## Third Party Advertising: 

Some of the ads appearing either on our Site, or within the newsletters distributed by the Site, may be delivered to you by our advertising partners. For more information about our advertising partners, cookies, and how to “opt-out”, please contact us for more information.

## Third party sites: 

As you know, we provide links to third party websites from the Site. These sites are not controlled by bestfoodrecipe.info and are therefore not covered by this Privacy Policy. We recommend that when you are directed away from the Site to a third party site you consult their privacy policy to check to way in which they deal with user information.

## Cookies: 

Like most sites, here at bestfoodrecipe.info we use browser “cookies.” Cookies are small text files placed on your computer’s hard drive by our server. This allows the website to remember who you are and will make your life all the more easy. For example, cookies will ensure that you are automatically taken to your counties home page or that you remain signed in (if you so wish). We promise never to use cookies to retrieve information from a computer that is unrelated to the Site or our services.

## Google Analytics: 

Here at bestfoodrecipe.info, our Site also uses Google’s web analytics tool “Google Analytics”. Google Analytics uses ‘cookies’ to track and collect anonymous information about the way in which you find and use the Site. It very helpfully produces a report of this data which we can then use to improve the Site and in turn, your bestfoodrecipe.info experience. As you know, a ‘cookie’ is a piece of data created when you visit the Site that is placed on your computer’s hard drive. This ‘cookie’ stores information, such as what time your visit occurred, whether you have been to the Site before, and how you arrived there. You can disable ‘cookies’ by using the appropriate feature of your web browser software, if available (see your internet browser provider’s website for more information). However, please note that if you do decide to ‘say no to cookies’ it is possible that this will affect the operation of the Site.

## Third Party Cookies: 

In the course of serving advertisements to the Site, or the newsletters distributed by the Site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

## Security: 

All the information described above is stored on our bestfoodrecipe.info restricted database servers. As far as reasonably possible we will endeavor to protect the information you entrust us with. However, such is the nature of the internet, no security system can be 100% secure. It is therefore important to note that you provide all such information at your own risk.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy:

bestfoodrecipe.info reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy from time to time without notice. Any such change will take effect once the revised policy is available on the Site.

## Contact Us:

Should you have any queries or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy please do not hesitate to get in touch.
